Michael Lewellen

michaelnlewellen@gmail.com | (469) 951-8107 michaellewellen.com | github.com/cylon56 | linkedin.com/in/michael-lewellen

SUMMARY

Been involved in the blockchain space as an investor and consultant since 2012. Adept at analyzing blockchain projects to determine viability. Specializes in blockchain development and whitepaper review. Experienced in explaining complex computer concepts to business professionals and finding use cases for blockchain technology in modern systems.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science University of Texas at Dallas Expected May 2019 Richardson, TX

SKILLS

- Fluent in Java, Solidity, and JavaScript. Some familiarity with C, C++, R and Python
- Experienced with Github, Visual Studio, IntelliJ, Vim, NodeJS, and MS Office
- Development experience on Windows and UNIX/Linux
- Completed B9Lab Ethereum Developer course covering Solidity, Truffle, and Web3

WORK EXPERIENCE

CryptoCurrency Consulting, LLC

Dallas, TX

Founder and Principal Consultant

October 2014 – present

- Founded a consulting firm for crypto in 2014: www.cryptocurrencyconsulting.com
- Provided consultations for mining, wallet security, and cryptocurrency trading
- Gave technical talks of how Bitcoin and blockchains work
- Developed and gave code audits for digital tokens and decentralized applications on Ethereum.
- Provided whitepaper reviews and deployment guidance for Initial Coin Offerings (ICO)

Olypsis Technologies

Richardson, TX

Blockchain Developer

February 2018 - present

- Developed, tested and deployed Ethereum smart contracts for ICO's including Rewards.com
- Worked with Thomson-Reuters to develop tax solutions using blockchain
- Provided project management and recruitment of additional developers

PixelHash Richardson, TX

Co-Founder and COO

October 2017 - February 2018

- Co-founded PixelHash, a digital asset creation and management platform for blockchain
- Built a proof of concept that integrates digital assets with video games on Ethereum

LEADERSHIP DEVELOPMENT

UT Dallas Blockchain Richardson, TX

President August 2017 - present

- Co-Founded the club, recruited officers, and made connections with the local business community
- Oversaw development workshops and industry speaker events
- Built a blockchain curriculum and ran the first student-organized blockchain hackathon

Other

• Event Organizer, Dallas Bitcoin Meetup 2013 - present

• Event Organizer, North Texas Blockchain Alliance 2017 - present

• BSA Eagle Scout, Troop 380, Longhorn Council 2008 - 2015

• Technology Director, Financial Leadership Association, UTD 2015 –2016